JASON QUAICOO

Haifa, Israel Jayquake@gmail.com +972-058-490-7209

SHORT ABOUT

As a new As a junior web developer, my passion for technology started with tinkering with electronics at the age of eight. I have a profound love for frontend development and scripting. My previous work experience working with students with special needs reinforced my attention to detail, spontaneity, and ability to think outside of the box. These skills have inspired me, pushed me forward, and provided me with a profound understanding and willingness to dive deeper into new technologies and web development.

HIGHLIGHTS

- Helped receive funding in an internship
- Developed strategies with a team
- •

QUALITIES

- Leadership
- Problem Solving
- Desire to learn

EDUCATION

DEVELOPERS INSTITUTE

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp- Python

github.com/jayquake

Completed coursework in HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL, Python.

MEDGAR EVERS COLLEGE

BSc. Nursing

Course Completed March. 2020

Brooklyn, NY Feb. 2015 - Dec. 2018

Tel Aviv. IL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CORONAVIRUS ACUTE MANAGEMENT APP

Full Stack Developer - Python, React, SQL

Brooklyn, NY April. 2020 - Current

- Worked on application to assist management of patients showing possible signs of COVID-19.
- Learned how to build a frontend application with the React framework

NYC DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION, P.S 207

Brooklyn, NY

Instructor

Jan. 2015 - Sept. 2019

- Taught small groups of students and assisted with the understanding and application of skills.
- Provided therapeutic interventions for children with developmental and emotional disabilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Javascript 6, React, Git, SQL, Python, Flask, Django, Google Analytics.